Preliminary Inventory of the Frank Farner Papers, 1957-1991
Hoover Institution Archives
Frank Farner Papers,
1957-1991
92057
Farner, Frank
27 manuscript boxes (11.2 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Speeches and writings, correspondence, reports, studies, memoranda, and printed matter, relating to the establishment and administration of Federal City College in Washington, D.C., and to activities of the World Bank in providing educational development assistance to various Asian countries, especially Bangladesh, Sri Lanka, Nepal, Thailand and China.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
Access Points
Federal City College.; Universities and colleges--United States.; Education--United States.; International Bank for Reconstruction and Development.; Educational assistance.; Education--Asia.; Education--Bangladesh.; Education--Sri Lanka.; Education--Nepal.; Education--Thailand.; Education--China.; Education.; United States--Foreign relations.; Asia.; Bangladesh.; Sri Lanka.; Nepal.; Thailand.; China.
Container List
- M.A. thesis, "The Relationship between Cultural-Linguistic Differences and Vocabulary Development and Achievement," 1957 (Box 1)
- Federal City College files, 1967-1969 (Box 1-8)
- United State (general) (Box 8)
- World Bank chronological files (Box 9)
  - 1976-1978
  - 1979-1981 (Box 10)
  - 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - 1988-1989 (Box 14)
- Asia (general) and the world (Box 15)
- Bangladesh (Box 15-16)
- China (Box 16-21)
- India (Box 21)
- Indonesia
- Malaysia
- Nepal (Box 21-23)
- New Guinea (Box 24)
- Pakistan
- Solomon Islands
- Sri Lanka (Box 25-26)
- Thailand (Box 26-27)